Finding Aid for the James G. Stahlman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Military and Aviation Careers - Correspondence
  - Incoming, Maddin - Mann (Box VII-11, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Manning - Markey (Box VII-11, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Marks - Martyn (Box VII-11, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Mason - Mazel (Box VII-11, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Meadors - Merrill (Box VII-11, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-11, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-11, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-12, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-13, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-13, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-13, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-13, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-13, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-13, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-13, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-13, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Merwin, Davis (Box VII-13, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Merwin, L. - Miller, H. (Box VII-13, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Miller, J. - Molter (Box VII-13, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Moncure - Morgan (Box VII-13, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Morris - Moss (Box VII-13, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Moss, Charles (Box VII-13, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Moss - Mumford (Box VII-13, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Munroe - Navy Department (Box VII-13, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Nelson - Nienoff (Box VII-13, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Nimitz (Box VII-13, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Nitze - Norris (Box VII-13, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Northrop, E. (Box VII-13, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Norvell - Ochs (Box VII-14, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, O’Connell - Paschal (Box VII-14, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Pate - Payne (Box VII-14, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Peace - Petrie (Box VII-14, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Pettey - Pittman (Box VII-14, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Piatt - Potter (Box VII-14, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Pounder - Prospective (Box VII-14, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Pryor - Radford (Box VII-14, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Ragsdale - Recruiting Inspector (Box VII-14, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Reece - Reeves (Box VII-14, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Reeves, J. W. (Box VII-14, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Reeves, J. W. (Box VII-14, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Refo - Fetired (Box VII-14, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Reynolds - Ricks (Box VII-14, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Riddell - Ridout (Box VII-14, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Riggs, W. F. (Box VII-14, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Righter - Roach (Box VII-14, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Roach, Agnes (Box VII-14, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Roberts - Robinson, F. (Box VII-14, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Robinson, F. - Roosevelt (Box VII-14, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Roper - Ryder (Box VII-15, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Sabin - Saunders (Box VII-15, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Sawyer - Schwanitz (Box VII-15, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Scoggins - Shearer (Box VII-15, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Sheehy - Shwab (Box VII-15, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Sibert - Sloan (Box VII-15, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Smith, A. - Smith, D. (Box VII-15, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Smith, E. - Smith, P. (Box VII-15, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Smith, R. - Sommers (Box VII-15, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Sorantin - Spruance (Box VII-15, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Stackhouse - Stahlman (Box VII-15, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Standley - Stark (Box VII-15, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Starkey - Stokes (Box VII-15, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Strauss - Symington (Box VII-15, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Tafe - Taylor (Box VII-15, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Tendler - Thach (Box VII-15, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Thacker - Thomason (Box VII-15, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Thompson (Box VII-15, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Thomson - Tode (Box VII-15, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Tolley - Tunney (Box VII-15, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Tupper - Tuthill (Box VII-16, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Tuthill - Upham (Box VII-16, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Van Blarcom - Van Zanot (Box VII-16, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Vance - Vining (Box VII-16, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Vining - Vinson (Box VII-16, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Walbridge - Walker (Box VII-16, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Wall - Washburn (Box VII-16, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Watson - Weems (Box VII-16, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Weer - Western (Box VII-16, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Westfall - Whitemarsh (Box VII-16, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Whiting - Wilhide (Box VII-16, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Wilkerson - Wilkinson (Box VII-16, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Willey - Williams, C. (Box VII-16, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Williams, C. - Williams, W. B. (Box VII-16, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Wilson, B. - Wilson, H. (Box VII-16, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Wilson, N. - Wolfe (Box VII-16, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Wolliner - Wynne (Box VII-16, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Yarnell - Zumwalt (Box VII-16, Folder 18)
- Military and Aviation Careers - Personal and Notes
  - Personal, Military Records, 1917 - 1945 (Box VII-17, Folder 1)
  - Personal, Military Subject Files, Clippings, 1924 - 1941 (Box VII-17, Folder 2)
  - Personal, Military Subject Files, 1942 - 1943 (Box VII-17, Folder 3)
  - Personal, Military Subject Files, 1944 - 1951, undated (Box VII-17, Folder 4)
  - Personal, Nashville Airport - Pan American Airways (Box VII-17, Folder 5)
  - Notes, Air Research Center - Military Unification (Box VII-17, Folder 6)
  - Notes, Nashville Airport - Yankee Clipper (Box VII-17, Folder 7)
- Military and Aviation Careers - Subject Files
  - Subject Files, American Airlines - Business Cards (Box VII-17, Folder 8)
  - Subject Files, Richard E. Byrd (Box VII-17, Folder 9)
  - Subject Files, Circumnavigators Club - Hampton Field (Box VII-17, Folder 10)
  - Subject Files, Harding - The “Hood”... (Box VII-17, Folder 11)
  - Subject Files, “Is Flying ...” - Korea (Box VII-17, Folder 12)
  - Subject Files, MacArthur - “Movie Cuties.. .” (Box VII-17, Folder 13)
  - Subject Files, Nashville Municipal Airport (Box VII-18, Folder 1)
  - Subject Files, Nashville Municipal Airport (Box VII-18, Folder 2)
  - Subject Files, Nashville Municipal Airport (Box VII-18, Folder 3)
  - Subject Files, Nashville Municipal Airport (Box VII-18, Folder 4)
  - Subject Files, Nashville Municipal Airport (Box VII-18, Folder 5)
  - Subject Files, Nashville Municipal Airport (Box VII-18, Folder 6)
  - Subject Files, Nashville Municipal Airport (Box VII-18, Folder 7)
  - Subject Files, Nashville Municipal Airport (Box VII-18, Folder 8)
  - Subject Files, Nashville Municipal Airport (Box VII-18, Folder 9)
  - Subject Files, Nashville Municipal Airport (Box VII-18, Folder 10)
  - Subject Files, Navy, “Address of...” - “Application of. ,12 Subject Files, Navy, Caribbean Cruise (Box VII-18, Folder 11)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Daily Digest (Box VII-18, Folder 13)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Defensive Management - Marine Corps (Box VII-19, Folder 1)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Military Unification (Box VII-19, Folder 2)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Military Unification, Clippings, Nov. 13, 1942 - Oct. 18, 1949 (Box VII-19, Folder 3)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Mlitary Unification, Clippings, Oct. 20, 1949 - Mar. 24, 1950 (Box VII-19, Folder 4)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Military Unification, Clippings, Jun. 5, 1950 - Sep. 18, 1953 (Box VII-19, Folder 5)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Misc. Clippings, Jun. 24, 1931 - Dec. 22, 1944 (Box VII-19, Folder 6)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Misc. Clippings, Mar. 17, 1945 - Dec. 17, 1949 (Box VII-19, Folder 7)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Misc. Clippings, Jan. 11, 1950 - Apr. 16, 1976 (Box VII-19, Folder 8)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Misc. Clippings, undated (Box VII-19, Folder 9)
  - Subject Files, Navy, “Naval News ...” - “Network Facilities.. .” (Box VII-19, Folder 10)
  - Subject Files, Navy, “Notes for ...” - “Pacific War.. .” (Box VII-19, Folder 11)
  - Subject Files, Navy, “Pay of...” - “Plan.. .” (Box VII-19, Folder 12)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Press Releases, Sep. 14, 1931 - Dec. 31, 1941 (Box VII-20, Folder 1)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Press Releases, Jan. 2 - Feb. 12, 1942 (Box VII-20, Folder 2)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Press Releases, Feb. 13, 1942 - Sep. 19, 1951 (Box VII-20, Folder 3)
  - Subject Files, Navy, “Radio Address.. .” - “Salute to.. .” (Box VII-20, Folder 4)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Strategic Bombing Myth, Agenda Items - “Comments On” (Box VII-20, Folder 5)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Strategic Bombing Myth, “Misrepresentation.. .” (Box VII-20, Folder 6)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Strategic Bombing Myth, Clippings, Jun. 16 - Dec. 11, 1949 (Box VII-20, Folder 7)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Strategic Bombing Myth, Clippings, Jan. 11, 1950 - Jan. 1, 1953, undated (Box VII-20, Folder 8)
  - Subject Files, Navy, Tanaka Memorial, Jul. 25, 1927 (Box VII-20, Folder 9)
  - Subject Files, Navy, U. S. Cable & Radio Censorship Regulations (Box VII-20, Folder 10)
  - Subj ect Files, Navy, US S Nashville (Box VII-20, Folder 11)
  - Subject Files, Navy, USS Tennessee (Box VII-20, Folder 12)
  - Subject Files, Navy, V-l Program (Box VII-20, Folder 13)
  - Subject Files, Navy, V-l Program (Box VII-20, Folder 14)
  - Subject Files, Navy, V-l Program (Box VII-20, Folder 15)
  - Subject Files, Navy, V-l Program (Box VII-21, Folder 1)
  - Subject Files, Navy, V-l Program (Box VII-21, Folder 2)
  - Subject Files, Navy, V-l Program (Box VII-21, Folder 3)
  - Subject Files, Navy, John Harlin Willis (Box VII-21, Folder 4)
  - Subject Files, Pan American Airways, Clipper Flights, 1934 - 1938 (Box VII-21, Folder 5)
  - Subject Files, Pan American Airways, Clipper Flights (Box VII-21, Folder 6)
  - Subject Files, Pan American Airways, Clipper Flights (Box VII-21, Folder 7)
  - Subject Files, Pan American Airways, Clipper Flights (Box VII-21, Folder 8)
  - Subject Files, Pan American Airways (Box VII-21, Folder 9)
  - Subject Files, Eddie Rickenbacker, Aug. 5, 1973 (Box VII-21, Folder 10)
  - Subject Files, World War II, Wake Island Report, undated (Box VII-21, Folder 11)
  - Subject Files, World War II, War Department Communiqués, Dec. 12 - 31, 1941 (Box VII-21, Folder 12)
  - Subject Files, World War II, War Department Communiqués, Jan. 1 - 31, 1942 (Box VII-21, Folder 13)
  - Subject Files, World War II, War Department Communiqués, Feb. 1 -Mar. 3, 1942 (Box VII-21, Folder 14)
  - Subject Files, World War II, “Welcome Home Song Sheet,”, undated (Box VII-22, Folder 1)
  - Subject Files, World War II, Articles, Clippings, Oct. 13, 1931 (Box VII-22, Folder 2)
- Military and Aviation Careers - Publications
  - Publications, Abilense ... - Aluminum... (Box VII-22, Folder 3)
  - Publications, America ... - Annual... (Box VII-22, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Aviation Industry (Box VII-22, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Bureau of... - Commerce of... (Box VII-22, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Congressional Record (Box VII-22, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Effects of Strategic Bombing on the German War Economy (Box VII-22, Folder 8)
  - Publications. First Line ... - Keeping Fit to Fight (Box VII-23, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Manual of ... - Naval Reserve Regulations (Box VII-23, Folder 2)
  - Publications, The Navy and Marine Corps (Box VII-23, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Navy Department - Navy Our First... (Box VII-23, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Navy’s Side - Now Is the Time... (Box VII-23, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Our Naw at War (Box VII-24, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Pan American ... - Planes (Box VII-24, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Register of Alumni (Box VII-24, Folder 3)
  - Publications. Register of Commissioned Officers (Box VII-25, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Register of Commissioned and Warrant Officers (Box VII-25, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Register of Commissioned and Warrant Officers (Box VII-25, Folder 3)
  - Publications. Register of Graduates (Box VII-26, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Register of Graduates (Box VII-26, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Strategic Bombing Myth (Box VII-26, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Statement bv Rear Administration Husband E. Kimmel..., undated (Box VII-26, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Unification and Strategy - US Naval Reserve (Box VII-26, Folder 5)
  - Publications, US Navy - Young America Speaks (Box VII-27, Folder 1)
- Military and Aviation Careers - Photographs and Negatives
  - Photographs, Atlantic Conference - Richard E. Byrd (Box VII-27, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Commander of... First Flight... (Box VII-27, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Hampton Field - Hepburn (Box VII-27, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Knox - Lejeune (Box VII-27, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Marine Corps - Nashville... (Box VII-27, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Panama Canal Zone - Pearl Harbor (Box VII-27, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Scholfied - Stahlman, James (Box VII-27, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Stahlman (Box VII-27, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, U.S. Navy Patrol... - USS Nashville (Box VII-27, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, US S Tennessee (Box VII-27, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, unidentified (Box VII-27, Folder 12)
  - Negatives, First World Flight (Box VII-27, Folder 13)
  - Negatives, Hampton Field (Box VII-27, Folder 14)
  - Negatives, Nashville Municipal Airport - Stahlman (Box VII-27, Folder 15)
  - Negatives, USS Tennessee (Box VII-27, Folder 16)
  - Negatives, unidentified (Box VII-27, Folder 17)
- Politics - Correspondence
  - Outgoing (Box VIII-1, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, 1937 - Jun. 1939 (Box VIII-1, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 1939-Feb. 1940 (Box VIII-1, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Mar. - Dec. 1940, undated 1940 (Box VIII-1, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, 1941 - Apr. 1942 (Box VIII-1, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, May 1942 - 1949 (Box VIII-1, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, 1950 - 1951 (Box VIII-1, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, 1952 - 1953 (Box VIII-1, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Jan. - Jun. 1954 (Box VIII-1, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 1954 - May 1955 (Box VIII-1, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Sep. - Dec. 1955 (Box VIII-1, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Jan. - Mar. 1956 (Box VIII-1, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, May - Sep. 10, 1956 (Box VIII-1, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 24 - 28, 1956 (Box VIII-1, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 1 - 4, 1956 (Box VIII-1, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 6 - Nov. 1956 (Box VIII-1, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 1956 - Apr. 1957 (Box VIII-1, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, May - Aug. 1957 (Box VIII-1, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 1957 - May 1958 (Box VIII-1, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Jan. - Dec. 1958 (Box VIII-1, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Jan. - Jul. 1959 (Box VIII-1, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 1959 - Feb. 1960 (Box VIII-1, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Jun. - Aug. 1, 1960 (Box VIII-1, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 2 - Sep. 19, 1960 (Box VIII-1, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 20 - 29, 1960 (Box VIII-1, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 3 - 24, 1960 (Box VIII-1, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 25 - Nov. 3, 1960 (Box VIII-1, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 4 - Dec. 1960 (Box VIII-1, Folder 28)
  - Outgoing (Box VIII-1, Folder 29)
  - Outgoing, Jan. - Jul. 1962 (Box VIII-2, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Oct. - Dec. 1962 (Box VIII-2, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 4 - 7, 1963 (Box VIII-2, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 8 - 10, 1963 (Box VIII-2, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 11 -28, 1963 (Box VIII-2, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 29 - Mar. 1963 (Box VIII-2, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, May - Sep. 1963 (Box VIII-2, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 3 - 19, 1963 (Box VIII-2, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 21 - Nov. 1963 (Box VIII-2, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 1963 - Mar. 2. 1964 (Box VIII-2, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 4 - Aug. 1964 (Box VIII-2, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 1964 - Dec. 1965 (Box VIII-2, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Jan. - Aug. 1966 (Box VIII-2, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 1966 - 1967 (Box VIII-2, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Jan. - Apr. 15, 1968 (Box VIII-2, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 16 - Oct. 1968 (Box VIII-2, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 1968 - May 1969 (Box VIII-2, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Jul. - Oct. 1969 (Box VIII-2, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 1969 - Jan. 1970 (Box VIII-2, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Feb. - Apr. 1970 (Box VIII-2, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, May - Sep. 1970 (Box VIII-2, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 1 - 17, 1970 (Box VIII-2, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 21 - Dec. 1970 (Box VIII-2, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Jan. - Mar. 1971 (Box VIII-2, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 1 - 7, 1971 (Box VIII-2, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 8 - Jun. 1971 (Box VIII-2, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 22 - Jul. 1971 (Box VIII-2, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 2-11, 1971 (Box VIII-3, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 12 - 30, 1971 (Box VIII-3, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Sep. - Oct. 1971 (Box VIII-3, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Nov. - Dec. 1971 (Box VIII-3, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Jan. - Mar. 1972 (Box VIII-3, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Apr. - Jul. 1972 (Box VIII-3, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Aug. - Sep. 1972 (Box VIII-3, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Oct. - Dec. 1972 (Box VIII-3, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 1973 (Box VIII-3, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Feb. - May 2, 1973 (Box VIII-3, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, May 13 - Jul. 16, 1973 (Box VIII-3, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 17 - Oct. 5, 1973 (Box VIII-3, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 22 - Dec. 1973 (Box VIII-3, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Jan. - Mar. 1974 (Box VIII-3, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Apr. - Aug. 1974 (Box VIII-3, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Sep. - Oct. 1974 (Box VIII-3, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 1974 - Feb. 1975 (Box VIII-3, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Mar. - Apr. 1975 (Box VIII-3, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, May - Jun. 1975 (Box VIII-3, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 1975 - Jan. 1976 (Box VIII-3, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Feb. - Apr. 28, 1976, undated (Box VIII-3, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Adams - Alexander (Box VIII-3, Folder 22)
  - Incoming, Allen (Box VIII-3, Folder 23)
  - Incoming, Alley - Andrews (Box VIII-3, Folder 24)
  - Incoming, Annenberg - Aycock (Box VIII-3, Folder 25)
  - Incoming, Baarslag - Baker, Howard (Box VIII-3, Folder 26)
  - Incoming, Baker, J. - Barnes (Box VIII-3, Folder 27)
  - Incoming, Barr - Bates (Box VIII-4, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Battle - Beard (Box VIII-4, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Beasley - Bermudez (Box VIII-4, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Berry - Bernrieder (Box VIII-4, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Bernrieder (Box VIII-4, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Bernrieder (Box VIII-4, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Bernrieder (Box VIII-4, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Bernrieder - Blankenship (Box VIII-4, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Blanton - Boyd (Box VIII-4, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Braden - Brock (Box VIII-4, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Brogan - Browning (Box VIII-4, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Buchanan - Byrd, Jr. (Box VIII-4, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Byrd, Jr. (Box VIII-4, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Byrd, Jr. - Calvert (Box VIII-4, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Campbell - Carter (Box VIII-4, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Cason - Clark, S. (Box VIII-4, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Clark, W. - Clement (Box VIII-4, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Clement (Box VIII-4, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Clement (Box VIII-4, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Clement (Box VIII-4, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Clement (Box VIII-4, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Clement (Box VIII-4, Folder 22)
  - Incoming, Clement (Box VIII-4, Folder 23)
  - Incoming, Cloud - Coles (Box VIII-5, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Collier - Cook (Box VIII-5, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Cornelius (Box VIII-5, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Corrigan - Crain (Box VIII-5, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Crichton - Cushman (Box VIII-5, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Daily - Davis (Box VIII-5, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Delgado - Dewolf (Box VIII-5, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Dickerson - Dixon (Box VIII-5, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Docking - Duckworth (Box VIII-5, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Dudley - Dunkleburger (Box VIII-5, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Dunn (Box VIII-5, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Durbrow - Egan (Box VIII-5, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Elsenhower (Box VIII-5, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Ellington (Box VIII-5, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Elliott - Ewing (Box VIII-5, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Fairfax - Farley (Box VIII-5, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Farley - Farris (Box VIII-5, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Fensterwald - Fitzgerald (Box VIII-5, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Fleming - Flint (Box VIII-5, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Flint (Box VIII-5, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Folk - Foster (Box VIII-5, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Foster (Box VIII-5, Folder 22)
  - Incoming, Foulon - Fulbright (Box VIII-5, Folder 23)
  - Incoming, Fulton - Fuqua (Box VIII-5, Folder 24)
  - Incoming, Galvin - Gay (Box VIII-5, Folder 25)
  - Incoming, General - Gold (Box VIII-6, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Goldwater (Box VIII-6, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Goughtly - Gore (Box VIII-6, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Gossett - Greene (Box VIII-6, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Greene - Guylay (Box VIII-6, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Hagerty - Hansen (Box VIII-6, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Hanson - Hartke (Box VIII-6, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Harvey - Hawkins (Box VIII-6, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Hays - Henry (Box VIII-6, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Hentschell - Hill (Box VIII-6, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Hilton - Hooker, H. (Box VIII-6, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Hooker, J. - Hooker, T. (Box VIII-6, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Hoover - Howard (Box VIII-6, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Huang - Hutton (Box VIII-6, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Ikard - Jewett (Box VIII-6, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Jimenez - Johnson, Lyndon (Box VIII-6, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Johnson, Lyndon B. (Box VIII-6, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Johnson, M. - Joyce (Box VIII-6, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Kachalim - Kenney (Box VIII-6, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, King - Klein (Box VIII-6, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Knight - Lampley (Box VIII-6, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Lawrence - Lillard (Box VIII-7, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Linder - Loeb, H. (Box VIII-7, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Loeb, W. (Box VIII-7, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Long - Loser (Box VIII-7, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Louthan - McCabe, B. (Box VIII-7, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, McCabe, T. - McEwen (Box VIII-7, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, McGill - McKellar (Box VIII-7, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, McKelway - Manno (Box VIII-7, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Marcley - Mason, F. (Box VIII-7, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Mason, F. (Box VIII-7, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Mason, F. (Box VIII-7, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Mason, F. (Box VIII-7, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Mason, F. - Matthews (Box VIII-7, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Maybank - Mickels (Box VIII-7, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Middleton - Miller (Box VIII-7, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Mills - Moley (Box VIII-7, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Moley (Box VIII-7, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Monks - Morrell (Box VIII-7, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Morris - Morton (Box VIII-7, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Moscon - Moss (Box VIII-7, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Moss, Charles (Box VIII-7, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Moss, Chase - Myers (Box VIII-7, Folder 22)
  - Incoming, Nabuco - Nellums (Box VIII-7, Folder 23)
  - Incoming, Nixon (Box VIII-8, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Nixon (Box VIII-8, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Nixon (Box VIII-8, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Noland - Ochsner (Box VIII-8, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Owen (Box VIII-8, Folder 5)